keystonerv.com 2017-06-23

# Keystone RV

_Effective December 22, 2011_

 **Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. We will not use or share your personal information provided to us online for any purpose other than to reply to your email, to contact you regarding customer service issues, warranty information, product information or to contact you regarding the submission of product ideas. We protect against unauthorized disclosures by limiting access only to those of our employees who need the information to do their jobs. We may also disclose information about you or your recreational vehicle as required by law, in conjunction with a government inquiry, a product recall or in litigation or dispute resolution. 

 **Children's Privacy  **  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under thirteen, please do not submit any personally identifiable information through our website. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personally identifiable information on our website without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to us through this website, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

 **Using the Information We Collect**  
We use the information we collect for various purposes, including:

  * to answer questions about your recreational vehicle;
  * to provide the services, parts, and repairs you request;
  * to send you our brochures and other offerings;
  * to contact you about the status of your dealer;
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you;
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased; and
  * to improve our products, customer service, and overall customer experience.

We may share information about you with our suppliers for the exclusive purpose of providing customer service, honoring the Keystone Limited Warranty or the various component warranties.

If you wish to be removed from any postal, email, phone or other lists, please let us know by phone or postal mail, or by emailing us at: [remove-me@keystonerv.com](mailto:remove-me@keystonerv.com&subject=Please%20remove%20me%20from%20your%20mailing%20list.). Please provide us with your exact name, address, and phone number. If you own a Keystone product we will need your vehicle identification number (VIN). We will be sure your name is removed from the appropriate list.

This website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

**Keystone will not share information about you or your recreational vehicle with any third party for their independent use without your permission.**

Keystone RV websites may contain links to third party websites, including websites owned or maintained by authorized Keystone RV dealers. The linked websites are not under the control of Keystone RV and Keystone is not responsible for the contents of any linked website or any link contained in a linked website. Keystone RV is providing these links only as a convenience and the inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked website by Keystone.  
 ****  
 **Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

 **Updating Your Contact Information**  
You can update or correct your name, address, telephone number, or email address by writing to us at Keystone RV Company,PO Box 2000, Goshen, Indiana 46527-2000, or by calling us at 1-574-535-2100.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.
